cakgames.com 2012-09-19

# Privacy Policy - Cakgames

Privacy Policy

#### Cakgames.com does not target its games and services to ages under 13, but we make a great deal of effort to protect those under 13. We do not ask users under the age of 13 to disclose any more information than necessary for them to participate in a particular activity (such as registering).

 **What information we collect**

To prevent abuse and enhance the features of our site, we collect non-personal information such as the IP (internet provider). Sometimes, we may store a file called a cookie on your computer. These non-malicious files are set to delete themselves within a short period of time (usually one day). They are used by us to help our advertisers target their traffic. A cookie may also be saved on your computer by our ad providers when you click an ad. This is saved on your computer so the advertisers can tell that you've already clicked an ad. This saves our advertisers from paying for double and fraudulent clicks. 

 **Third-Party Advertising  **

Cakgames uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

 **We only collect necessary information**

The information we collect is only the information which is necessary. No personally identifiable information (such as your phone number, address, name etc) is ever collected unless you have willingly submitted it such as through registration.

 **Security**

To ensure the highest amount of privacy,  Cakgames.com is equipped with many security features to protect our files from unauthorized access.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

The contents of this policy may be altered at any time, at our discretion. 

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of, please contact us at cakgames[at]hotmail.co.id

Thanks   
Cakgames Crew .
